this exercise
asks us whether hash values can be
arrays
and whether we can have an array of
hashes so let's hop into irb
and experiment with this let's write a
hash
and our key will be names now this value
can be an array
so let's give it an array of strings
here you can see we've got a hash with
one key value pair
the key is the symbol names and the
value is an array of strings
now let's take a look at an array of
hashes so i'll write out an array
and let's give it several hashes with
one key value pair
each one of these will have a symbol as
the key
and a string as the value
so now we've got a three element array
and each of those elements
is a hash
so this is definitely possible and
you'll see nested collections like this
frequently
you